leasetrader.com 2006-06-15

# Privacy Statement - LeaseTrader.com

**THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

At LeaseTrader.com you can take-over a lease, post a lease, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

At LeaseTrader.com you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and e-mail address to send an electronic message and you might submit the recipient's name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.  
At certain parts of some of our sites, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the site's activities and offerings.

In order to use some features of this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest.   
We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '95 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).

**HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION**

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.  
We sometimes use this information to communicate with you about our services, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them information to offer our products, programs, or services to them.  
We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

Agents and contractors of LeaseTrader who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for LeaseTrader.com.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.

We may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, click here for instructions on how to make your request.

**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD-PARTY SITES AND SPONSORS**

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

LeaseTrader.com may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or co branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. LeaseTrader has no control over these third parties' use of this information. LeaseTrader.com will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.

Our privacy policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party ad server may have collected from you. For more information on this site's use of such third-party ad servers, please click here.

**OUR COMMITMENT TO SECURITY**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, please contact our Customer Service Manager by E-Mail or by Postal Mail to:

Customer Service Manager   
LeaseTrader.com   
1835 E. Hallandale Blvd.   
Suite 431   
Hallandale, Florida 33009
